See you later, Origami.
Yeah, later.
Mom and Dad.
Oh, no.
What happened?
It's your fault.
You!
I won't forgive you!
Ever!
I'm gonna kill you!
I swear!
Someday, I will!
Good morning, little bed buddy.
Ah!
Sharing a bed is so dreamy.
All the romance and sweetness.
If only it could last beyond the morning.
What a paradise life would be.
Is there a favor?
Itusta no building.
Very sweet.
See you next time.
No, I'm not!
And how were you able to transform anyway?
Right, I never told you about that.
The deal with Natsumi, I mean.
What?
Wait, was the seal incomplete or something?
Oh, no.
The seal itself was actually successful.
So, are the transformations triggered by her emotions then?
Yeah, I guess that's one way of putting it.
She's not the most stable in case you haven't picked that up.
No fair.
What are you two whispering about over there?
Fear of missing out has always been kind of a thing with me.
Just look at her.
You gotta do something about transforming over every little thing.
Listen, I totally get that you're jealous that Shido fell for me.
But it's not my fault your body is so inferior to my voluptuous one.
It's not my fault I'm a munchkin!
I happen to be having a growth spurt!
You're the cutest!
Stop laughing immediately!
Look at your red little face!
Shut up, you horny!
Origami still hasn't shown up.
That was obviously one of DEM's CR units.
So, what does this mean?
I don't get it.
Where is she?
Stand!
Bow!
Sit!
Um, before I take attendance,
I'm afraid I have a rather sad announcement to make, everyone.
Whoa.
What's up, Temmy girl?
Did the matchmaking not work out?
Oh, snap!
Are you catfish?
That is so lame!
Ahem.
No, actually.
Origami Tobiichi will be transferring to another school
due to unexpected circumstances.
Transferring?
Transfer?
Hold on, back up.
What do you mean?
What exactly is going on?
Unfortunately, I don't really have any other details.
I got a call from her out of the blue and all she said was that she was transferring.
She said she'd send in the forms later on.
No!
Did she say what school she's going to?
Oh, well, she sort of did.
She said something about a school in England.
England?
I see.
You okay, Itsuka?
Um, it's just...
my stomach!
Yeah, it's been really hurting me today.
She...
You stay where you are!
I'll be fine!
Ah!
Why do I have to be the way that I am?
Um, here I finally got up early enough.
I never meant to wake him up while I was in that form.
Thanks a lot for the tea, Natsumi!
Me?
Sure, no sweat.
So is there something you need from me?
Oh, um...
Funny you ask.
What could possibly bring this one to my room?
I can't even guess.
Oh, I know.
I bet she bears some kind of grudge and came to get revenge!
The truth is, I was thinking that since you just moved in, you probably don't know the city all that well and you might like some hope.
That's right!
That has to be it!
After all, I was fooling Shido by impersonating her little friend!
I mean, it's not like I know all there is to know either!
So I actually may not be all that helpful to you.
She waited until all the others were gone to make her move!
But if you're interested, I would be more than happy to show you around the city!
Huh?
It's just that I've always spent this time of day all by myself.
But since you're here now, well, I was hoping that you and I could spend some time hanging out together.
Because... well, just because... we're friends, aren't we?
Whoa! I've gotta marry this girl!
Hey, if you're willing to show me around the city, then heck yeah, I'll take you up on it!
When do we leave? Let's go already!
I'm sorry. The number you've dialed is out of the service area.
Please hang up and try again.
Why isn't she picking up?
Hope you're here, Origami.
Okay, I've made it inside.
Origami! It's me! Say something if you're there!
It's open!
Origami!
Where in the world did you run off to? And for what?
Your lunch looks so yummy, Coterie!
Plunk, thanks. My brother made it for me.
Now let's eat!
What do you mean you can't find Shido? He's in class, isn't he?
It seems he skipped out as soon as he heard about Origami transferring schools.
Well, that's weird. Doesn't that timing seem suspicious? Missing at the same time? What about the others?
Toka, the Yumai sisters, and Miku are all having lunch at their respective schools.
And Natsumi and Yoshino apparently went out to play in the city together.
Gotcha.
Well, I'd hate to make everyone worry, but we can't keep it from them forever.
We need to find Shido fast, before all the others get home.
Where am I?
What happened at Origami's?
It's you! Where have you been? Why were you...
Water. Bet you're a little thirsty.
I...
Um...
Yeah.
Hey, stop! What are you doing?
Yes, I want some, but only the normal way!
Thanks. Real slow...
Look, can you help me out? Just untie me.
That I can't do.
It's true. You really joined D.E.M.
Yes.
And my abduction? Did Westcott order you to do this to me?
This is all me. I brought you here of my own volition.
D.E.M. is completely unaware that I kidnapped and brought you here today.
This is the only way to get it done.
If I was going to keep you out of it, this method held the strongest chance for success.
Hold on a sec. What do you mean, keep me out? Out of what?
My fight is only with the spirits.
My spirits? You mean...
Of course. You know I mean them too. No exceptions.
Wait! I thought the point was that you were after the spirit who killed your parents!
Toka and the others had nothing to do with it!
But spirits are all the same. If we're going to keep more humans like me from being created, then we simply cannot allow them to continue existing.
But Toka and the others don't even register as spirits!
Remember? You told me you didn't have to go after them anymore!
That was a self-defense force decision. It has nothing to do with me now.
Think, Murakami. It's been over six months since I met Toka, and she transferred to our school.
Man, time flies. Now the spirits you guys used to fight are a regular part of our society. Not only that, they're a part of our lives!
So how can you, you who have been here through all of it, how can you look at them and say they haven't changed?
That it's once a spirit, always a spirit! That they're so dangerous, they need to be murdered!
You really think I don't get it? Toka and all the others have drawn me in too, but they're spirits all the same.
Seeing them should feed my revenge, and yet it hasn't.
I can never forgive myself for slowly losing sight of my goal.
Five years ago, I swore I'd get revenge for the death of my parents.
But now I live amongst my enemies. I've been so weak.
The reason I decided to join DEM was because I realized how wrong I'd been.
That in accepting Tokayatogami, I was betraying everything I believed.
But that's because what you believed was wrong! You know them as well as I do!
They're peaceful! All they want is to live normal lives!
No. I can't allow that. They are what they are, Shido.
I have more to destroy than just spirits. I have to kill the girl in me who chose to take the easy way out.
I'll regain the person I was by taking the life of Tokayatogami.
Origami, wait! Please come back!
And you're okay with it, Ike? Allowing her to act on her own like this?
Doesn't matter to me.
I'm glad she's showing some initiative.
There's no sense dampening the enthusiasm of a young wizard, in my opinion.
Remember, in the end, what we're after are spirits.
And the only way to measure the power of a bomb is to simply let it drop.
Be honest, aren't you a little curious about how far she'll go if given the chance?
Very well, then. I'll do whatever I can behind the scenes.
You're displeased, though. I can tell because your brows wrinkle right here when you have to lie.
Just kidding.
Come on, don't be mad at me. It just so happens that I have another target in mind for you this time.
We have another target?
Yes. Ratadisker. They have a certain ship that's going to get in Origami's way.
And I want you to stop it. Using Goetia, naturally.
Can't believe a tummy ache sent Shido home.
He's too weak. We need to train him back up into shape.
Agreed. He's turned into a wimpy wimp. Starting tomorrow, we'll make him run laps.
I'm sure he had a good reason for leaving.
Question. I've heard people saying that Master Origami has transferred schools for some reason.
Do we think Shido leaving could be related to that?
Yeah. In fact, that's exactly when he left, right after he found out about Origami.
See, I so knew that. It smelled fishy to me the whole time.
You can smell fish? How weird. I can't smell anything.
That's not really what I meant.
Hey, Toka! And Kaguya! I'm Yuzuru!
Huh? Why on earth would you choose to dodge my expression of love?
Oh, that's what that was?
Oh, duh, of course. It's the new thing everyone's doing. Come on, bring it on in!
Don't be fooled, kinswoman.
Warning. I definitely smell a liar.
Aha! I knew it. For starters, what the heck are you doing here anyway?
Right. Kay. I came out to visit Darling, but no one was there, so it was super boring.
And then the house next door was empty, too.
So you mean Shido hasn't come home yet?
What about the Origami thing? I have a feeling that she has something to do with this.
Agreement. I think we might actually be onto something.
You guys! Would someone please tell me what the heck is going on? Did something happen to my darling?
Here's the deal. Right now?
Why is the spatial quake alarm going off?
I guess we should assume another spirit showed up.
Curious. Should we all go see who this spirit is?
No, we can't do that! You know that if the alarm is sounding, that means we have to evacuate!
I know, but Shido...
There's no need for that.
Origami-Tobiichi? What are you doing here?
There is no spatial quake.
What do you mean? There must be! Just listen!
The alarm is sounding, because I put in a request for it to do so.
Neither a spirit nor the AST are going to show up.
But why? What would make you do something like that?
To make it easier to kill the rest of you!
I said, the point is to kill you! To kill all spirits!
Look at your eyes!
Oh no...
Why have you gone back to before Origami-Tobiichi?
So, you noticed us!
Respect. This is our Master Origami.
Now then, how about explaining what this is all about?
Inquiry. Please answer our call, Master Origami.
We have no desire to fight you today.
I don't have to answer anything!
I don't have to answer ANYTHING!
Send-o fun!
Gabriel! RONDO!
No!
Hey, you guys! Is everyone okay?
Origami isn't playing a game.
If we don't kill her, we'll be killed.
What are you doing, Toga?!
Origami? Where the hell did she come from?
Such great magical power.
She's on a whole other level than before.
Without their full spirit armor, the others aren't safe.
Fraxinus, full power ahead.
Let's go get them out of there.
If it gets ugly, deploy the Ectrifolium.
Let's back them up!
Roger!
What was that?
We're now under attack. Territory reduced 30%.
Enemy in our sights at 3 o'clock.
It's... an airship!
Are you serious?!
Oh, great. It's DEM.
What perfect timing.
A transmission.
Really?
Yes, coming from said ship.
They're trying to reach out to the Fraxinus.
Fine. Connect us.
Right.
Well, nice to meet you, I suppose.
I appreciate you accepting the transmission.
Wait, you're Ellen Mathers.
I guess that means you've heard of me then.
It's an honor, Kotari Itsuka.
Okay, so what business does the world's strongest wizard have with us today?
If you want to drink tea and chat, let's do it later.
I'm a little busy right now.
You see, a vile organization's troublesome pawn is picking a fight with our girls.
I have two things to say.
Number one, I'll give you up to three minutes to get out of here.
Anyone who would like to live should leave the ship without hesitation.
You honestly believe that you could take down Fraxinus, don't you?
All I'll say is I can't deny the possibility that it might happen.
But seriously, Fraxinus?
As in the tree of life.
I assume Elliot must have chosen the name.
Don't you think you might be underestimating Fraxinus just a little bit?
With all due respect, perhaps you're the person who's been doing the underestimating here.
Of my Goetia's abilities as well as my power.
Cool. Is there anything else you want to say?
Yes. Only to the one who fled this conflict.
I have a message for you to give to Elliot.
A message?
Yes. Elliot. I hate you. You're a disgusting traitor.
You turned your back on us in the promise we made.
Prepare yourself. No matter where you hide, I swear I'm gonna find you.
I'm going to have your head.
That's all.
Starting now, I'll give you three minutes to evacuate.
Please leave as quickly as you can.
Well, you heard her. We're about to be up against humanity's best, so if you want to run, you should do it now.
Gimme a break. If I was ever gonna run away, I would have done so a dozen times before now.
Yeah. Leaving all this behind and running? How is that any different than death?
Damn right. Who cares if it's humanity's greatest? I say we go show her what we've got.
Say the word. I'm ready. My will is written and good to go.
And the hard drive from my computer back home is set to a race if anything happens to me, so I'm ready. I'm in.
But it's so hard to pass up being punished by you for running.
Oh! Well, there you have it.
Is that so? Such a shame.
AR-008, give three to six parallel driving force. Replenish magic power. Ready, Mistleteen. Target, DEM airship, go ATF!
Roger!
Coterie Itsuka, I thought you were capable of rational thought, but I guess I must have been mistaken.
You and he may not share any blood, but you're truly Shido Itsuka's sister.
Best compliment ever.
Kanazuki, deploy Interfolium 1 through 12. It's the world's strongest wizard. Let's be prepared, just in case.
You know, somehow I knew you'd say that.
Let's clean things up here, then we'll go get Touka and the girls.
Replenishment complete. Mistleteen, ready to fire.
Enemy ship Goetia hasn't moved.
Sitting pretty for three whole minutes. She doesn't think we're serious.
Mistleteen, fire!
You're kidding me! What was that speed?
I think they must have thinned out the territory surrounding the ship.
That would maximize their mobility.
As for that driving force, best guess, they probably used territory to flick the ship aside.
Wait, you're saying that's actually possible?
Oh, sure. Theoretically, it could be done.
And I suppose we should expect nothing less from the Immortal Matters.
This is no time to be impressed! She's coming!
Protect territory! Breeze for impact!
Oh, man, you've really done it now!
Prepare counterattack! Eat your folium to mine mode!
Get them behind her, fast!
Roger.
What now?
Another blast! Bombardment!
No!
Help! Anyone! Is anyone out there? Anyone!
Oh, man!
You're the one!
No!
ED
See you next time.